All right then, gang.So I want to move away from prompting context commands and sub agents now and move on to another nice feature in Claude Code, which is the Claude Code GitHub app.And this is something we can set up easily from within the Claude Code chat session.And I'm going to show you how to do that in a moment.But basically, when we install it, creates 2 GitHub actions for us automatically, which are both really useful.The first one is that it can auto review pull requests and provide feedback on those pull requests.
好的，各位。我想從提示詞、上下文、指令和子代理的話題轉移， 來介紹 Claude Code 中另一個很棒的功能——Claude Code GitHub 應用程式。 我們可以在 Claude Code 聊天作業階段中輕鬆設定它，我現在就來示範。 基本上，安裝後它會自動為我們建立兩個 GitHub Actions，兩個都非常實用。 第一個是它能自動審查拉取請求並提供回饋。
The second one allows Claude code to automatically work on issues on a new feature branch when you mention @claude inside it.Now, before I show you how to set up this feature, I will say that you need to have the GitHub CLI already installed on your computer, which you can do by following these installation instructions.So I'm going to leave a link to this repo down below the video.But essentially, you can just install it via something like Homebrew on a Mac or WinGet on Windows.
第二個允許 Claude Code 在 Issue 中提及 @claude 時， 自動在新功能分支上處理該 Issue。 在展示如何設定這個功能之前，我要說你需要先在電腦上安裝 GitHub CLI， 你可以按照這些安裝說明進行，我會在影片下方附上這個倉庫的連結。 基本上，在 Mac 上可以透過 Homebrew，在 Windows 上可以透過 WinGet 來安裝。
It's all really simple to do, and it outlines the steps in this README file.Once you've installed the GitHub CLI, you'll also need to log in by running this command in your terminal, GH auth login.Once you've done that, you're ready to set up the Claude Code GitHub app.All right, so inside Claude Code, we can use a built-in slash command, which is forward slash install hyphen GitHub app.and I'm going to press enter here.What that does is set up the GitHub actions for the repository that we want to give it access to.
一切都非常簡單，這個 README 檔案中列出了所有步驟。 安裝完 GitHub CLI 後，你還需要在終端機中執行以下指令進行登入：gh auth login。 完成後，你就準備好設定 Claude Code GitHub 應用程式了。 好的，在 Claude Code 中，我們可以使用一個內建斜線指令 /install-github-app，然後按 Enter。 這個指令會為我們想要授權的倉庫設定 GitHub Actions。
So I'm going to press enter and then it's going to ask us which repository we want to use.We can enter a different one if we want, but I'm going to use the one linked up to this local repo right here that I'm in.So I'm going to press enter on this option.Then it's going to open a browser and it's going to ask us to install Claude code on GitHub.So let's click the install button over here.We need to authorize it.Now you can choose toit access to all repositories or only select repositories.
我要按 Enter，它會詢問我們要使用哪個倉庫。 我們可以輸入不同的倉庫，但我要使用與我目前所在本地倉庫連結的那個， 所以我要按 Enter 選擇這個選項。 然後它會開啟瀏覽器，要求我們在 GitHub 上安裝 Claude Code。 讓我們點擊這裡的安裝按鈕。需要進行授權， 你可以選擇授予它存取所有倉庫的權限，或者只選擇特定倉庫。
I'm just going to select this one to give it access to the Claude Code tutorial one, which is this down here.
我只打算選擇這一個，授予它存取 Claude Code 教學倉庫的權限，就是這裡這個。
And then I'm going to install and authorize this.And then once you've authenticated it and installed it on your GitHub account, you can just come back to the terminal and press enter to complete this.And it says select GitHub workflows to install.We're going to install both of them.I'm just going to press enter andAnd then we're just going to choose the first option here, create a long-lived token with your Claude subscription.It's going to ask you to authorize with your Claude code account.So I'm going to do that.
然後我要安裝並授權它。 一旦你完成驗證並在 GitHub 帳戶上安裝後， 可以回到終端機按 Enter 完成設定。 它說選擇要安裝的 GitHub 工作流程，我們要安裝兩個，直接按 Enter。 然後選擇第一個選項：使用你的 Claude 訂閱建立長期存取 Token。 它會要求你使用你的 Claude Code 帳戶進行授權，我要這樣做。
Once you've authenticated with Anthropic, it's going to ask you to create this pull request.And this is basically two actions that it's created.It explains everything down here.We can just create this pull request.
完成 Anthropic 驗證後，它會要求你建立這個拉取請求。 這基本上是它建立的兩個 Actions，下面說明了一切。 我們可以直接建立這個拉取請求。
And then one of the actions is to automatically review pull requests, and down here we're just waiting for some checks to be completed.Once they've completed, you can merge that request, and now up here, if we go to actions, we should be able to see we've got these two actions right here: Claude Code and Claude Code Review.Okay, so now we're ready to put Claude Code to use in the GitHub repository.
其中一個 Action 是自動審查拉取請求，下面我們正在等待一些檢查完成。 完成後，你可以合併那個請求， 現在如果我們點選 Actions，應該就能看到這兩個 Actions： Claude Code 和 Claude Code Review。 好的，現在我們準備好在 GitHub 倉庫中使用 Claude Code 了。
And I'm going to create an issue in a second, and the issue is going to be that this title over here doesn't link to anywhere, and ideally, it should link to this page, the homepage.So let's create an issue and tell Claude Code to handle this.All right then, so let's head to issues, and we're going to create a new issue.We'll just say link from title missing, and then I'll say there is no
我馬上要建立一個 Issue：這裡的標題沒有連結到任何地方， 理想情況下它應該連結到這個頁面——首頁。 讓我們建立一個 Issue，告訴 Claude Code 來處理這個問題。 好的，讓我們前往 Issues，建立一個新 Issue，就說「缺少標題連結」， 然後說：導覽列標題
link from the title in navbar to the homepage.All right, so I'm going to create this issue.Now, nothing happens automatically, but if I come down here and mention Claude, I can just say at Claude and I'll say, can you fix this?
沒有連結到首頁。好的，我要建立這個 Issue。 現在什麼事都不會自動發生， 但如果我在這裡提及 Claude，輸入 @claude，然後說：你能修復這個嗎？
I'm going to comment over here and hopefully just after a minute or so, Claude is going to start work on this task.
我要在這裡留言，希望過一兩分鐘後，Claude 就會開始處理這個任務。
And you can see now Claude has picked it up and it's starting to work on this issue.
你現在可以看到 Claude 已經接收到它，並開始處理這個 Issue。
All right, so it's created this little to-do list, much like it does in Claude code within the terminal, and it's looking at the different things it needs to do, examining the current navbar, adding the link for the title, it's going to test it, then it's going to commit and push the changes, then it's also going to provide a PR creation link, which we can go and take a look at.
好的，它建立了一個小待辦清單，就像在終端機的 Claude Code 中一樣， 列出了它需要做的不同事項： 檢查現有的導覽列、為標題新增連結、測試、 然後提交並推送變更，接著還要提供建立 PR 的連結供我們查看。
All right, so it's finished its little to-do list now, and there's a summary down here to say that it's fixed it and any changes that have been made.It's also created the PR, or rather it gives us a link to create the PR based on this edit.So, if we go there, it's pre-populated this description and also the title for the PR.I'm going to create this pull request.And when we create a pull request, Claude Code automatically picks up on the pull request and provides us with a code review.
好的，它現在完成了待辦清單， 下面有一個摘要說明它已修復了問題以及所做的更改。 它也建立了 PR，或者說它給了我們一個連結，根據這次編輯來建立 PR。 如果我們前往那裡，描述和標題都已預先填入。我要建立這個拉取請求。 當我們建立拉取請求時，Claude Code 會自動接收到並為我們提供程式碼審查。
And you can see now down here, the Claude Code review is going in the background.Okay, so now it's finished each review and we can see the feedback down here.We get a big green tick, which means it's pretty good overall.So we get a tick for code quality, a tick for bugs, a tick for performance and security.Overall, it says approve.Yep.All right, so let's go down here.We can merge the pull request now and confirm the merge.
你現在可以看到 Claude Code 審查正在背景執行。 好的，現在它完成了審查，我們可以在這裡看到回饋。 我們看到一個大大的綠色勾，表示整體上看起來不錯。 所以我們在程式碼品質、錯誤、效能和安全性上都得到了勾，整體評估為批准。 好的，讓我們往下看，現在我們可以合併拉取請求並確認合併。
Okay, so I just pulled down those changes so we can preview this in a browser.And now if we hover over this title, you can see it goes purple, we get the little pointer icon, and if we click on it, it goes to the homepage.Awesome.So that's now working.So then that's how Claude Code can work directly in your central GitHub repository.And I think it's quite a nice addition to the product.You can also make additional actions, by the way, to include Claude Code in different ways and different workflows.
好的，我剛拉取了那些變更，這樣我們就可以在瀏覽器中預覽了。 現在如果我們將游標移到這個標題上，可以看到它變成紫色，出現了小指標圖示， 點擊後它會跳到首頁。很棒，現在它正常運作了。 這就是 Claude Code 如何直接在你的 GitHub 倉庫中運作。 我認為這是產品中相當不錯的新增功能。 順帶一提，你也可以製作額外的 Actions，以不同的方式和工作流程中使用 Claude Code。
So it's definitely worth looking through the action files and playing around with them.
所以絕對值得查看那些 Action 檔案並試著玩玩看。